OUTSYSTEM DEVELOPER

About me

I graduated from Ongku Omar Polytechnic with diploma in Mechanical engineering. Previously, I worked in Samsung Service Center Sunway Pyramid as a Technician. I found my passion and interested in software development since 2022. Therefore, I joined an online coding school which is sigma school to learn coding. Recently, I learn about Outsystem and build an enterprise application such as Employee Directory Application.

Experience

Technician/Engineer, June 2021 to June 2022

Samsung Service Center - Sunway Pyramid

- Explained to customer for mobile or tablet issue.
- Contacted customer for collection if devices are repair completed.
- Performed diagnostics and troubleshooting to evaluate equipment performance and increase reliability.
- Wrote technical report one-time warranty policy for repair devices with three months period which client could return their devices for warranty service.
- Called customers for repair quotation.
- Format devices if customers required.

Admin, 03/2020-01/2021

Thiyagrajan Contractor-Teluk Intan, Perak, Malaysia

- Filled documentation.
- Followed up calls and messages with suppliers and customers.
- Searched for materials for government projects.
- Key in financial data into SQL accounting software.

Attended Course

Sigma School- online coding school

• Software development

Qualification

Diploma, Mechanical engineering 2018 Ungku Omar polytechnics-

Ipoh.Perak.

- CGPA 3.51
- Anugerah Khas Ketua Jabatan Sesi Disember 2017
- Anugerah Khas Ketua Jabatan Sesi June 2016 Member of Chess Club

SMK Raja Muda Musa-Teluk Intan,Perak.

Anugerah cemerlang SPM 5A 2014



Name: Lim Chin Hong

Age: 27

Data of Birth: 1996-06-18 Marital status: Single

Contact

Address:36000, Perak, Teluk Intan, Malaysia.

Phone: +6016-876 7633

Email: rexes_123@hotmail.com

Porfolio website:

https://portfolio-website-xi-mauve.vercel.app/

Skills

Intermediate

- Html
- CSS
- Javascript
- Wordpress
- OutSystem

Beginner

- Node.js
- Vue.js
- PostgreSQL
- Insomia for Rest API

Language

• **Chinese**: Advanced

• **English**: Upper intermediate

• **Malay**: Upper intermediate